我的天
Oh, my God
这下麻烦了
This is bad
我觉得还可以抢救一哈
Actually, not too bad
不应该浪费我们的燃料……
There is no point using our fuel
来转个圈~
Rotate 360 degrees
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
海上降落
Ocean landing
转速67到68转每分钟
Rotation is 67 - 68 RPM
留好提前量，好把它带回陆地
Achieve enough margin to bring it all  the way back to land
这不可能
It's not possible
如果你觉得重要，那就去做吧，不要管什么胜算如何
If something is important enough you do it even if the odds are not in your favor
说起来有点土
This may sound corny
但真爱就是答案
but love is the answer
你又在干嘛？
What are you doing?
没时间去……
This is no time for...
有过很多次模拟
There are many, many simulations
这些模拟可能不是……
These simulations aren't...
我们所说的现实
may as well call them reality
或者你可以说它们是平行宇宙
or you can call them multiverse
整个飞行过程没有任何外部控制参与
No controls touched at any point during entire journey
EZ~
Easy
还是很让我津津乐道的
It's still tripping me out
我是说我真的念念不忘此事
I mean I'm tripping balls here